[
    {
        "type": "identification",
        "question": "Style of programming",
        "answer": "Language Paradigm"
    },

    {
        "type": "identification",
        "question": "Based on the concept of objects (state and behavior)",
        "answer": "Object-oriented"
    },

    {
        "type": "identification",
        "question": "Utilizes control flow constructs.",
        "answer": "Structured"
    },
    {
        "type": "identification",
        "question": "Mimics a function in mathematics. ",
        "answer": "Functional"
    },
    {
        "type": "identification",
        "question": "Uses facts and rules.",
        "answer": "Logic"
    },
    {
        "type": "identification",
        "question": "The implementation of the design phase in the SDLC",
        "answer": "Application development stage"
    },


    {
        "type": "multiple-choice",
        "question": "Translate source code (written in a programming language) into the computer language (object code)",
        "options": [
            "Compiler",
            "Interpreter",
            "Assembler",
            "Decompiler"
        ],
        "answer": "Compiler"
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple-choice",
        "question": "Used in assembly language to convert the source code into the machine language",
        "options": [
            "Compiler",
            "Interpreter",
            "Assembler",
            "Decompiler"
        ],
        "answer": "Assembler"
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple-choice",
        "question": "“reverse-engineer” the translation performed by compilers and assemblers",
        "options": [
            "Compiler",
            "Interpreter",
            "Assembler",
            "Decompiler"
            
        ],
        "answer": "Decompiler"
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple-choice",
        "question": "Translate source code into the target machine code “on-the-fly” (reads source code, converts it and executes it directly)",
        "options": [
            "Compiler",
            "Interpreter",
            "Assembler",
            "Decompiler"
        ],
        "answer": "Interpreter"
    }

    
]